http://www.mackays.com/privacy-policy/

Navigation
Our RangeMarmaladesPreservesCurdsChutneysGift PacksStockist searchFlavour finderBuy onlineOur StoryHow we craftOur fruitsDundee MarmaladeOur Copper Pans
The Preservation SocietyJoin the societyRecipesContact usGet in touchMackays FAQsPress & MediaInternational Site
Close
Mackays
Privacy policy
Please hold tight, we are updating out Privacy Policy as we speak.
Mackays Limited a company incorporated in Scotland and having its registered office at Mackays Ltd, James Chalmers Road, Arbroath, DD11 3LR, Scotland
("we" or "us") are committed to preserving your privacy. Please read the following privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to understand how we use and protect the Personal Data (as defined in the Data Protection Act 1988) ("Data") that you provide to us.
By submitting your Data to us, you consent to the collection, storage, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Data That We Collect From You
We collect Data about you:
when you request services or otherwise provide us with your personal details (such as your name, contact details, e-mail address etc); and
from your usage of the Site and any other information you post on the Site, e-mail or otherwise send to us.
We may contact you by post, telephone or fax as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future by any of these means then please let us know.
Disclosure Of Your Data
The Data you provide to us will be treated as confidential. However, we may disclose your Data to other third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or for purposes approved by you.
In addition, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your Data may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.
Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the Data you provide to us without your consent.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a piece of software that attaches to the hard drive of your computer and remembers information about the configuration of your computer.
We use this information to track your movements through our Site, to find out how it is being used and to assess its usefulness. Personal information about you is not collected during the tracking process.
You can disable the cookies that we attach if your browser supports this. For further information on how to do this, please refer to www.allaboutcookies.org. However, you should bear in mind that if you exercise this option, you may be unable to use some of our on-line services.
Third Party Websites
Because we want your experience of our Site to be as informative and useful as possible, we provide a number of links to websites operated by third parties ("Third Party Websites"). Please be aware that we do not control such Third Party Websites and that such Third Party Websites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. We assume no responsibility for the information gathering practices of Third Party Websites that you are able to access through our Site, and we encourage you to review each Third Party Website's privacy policy before disclosing any personally identifiable information.
Security
We employ security measures to protect your Data from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction or damage.
Please help us keep our records updated by informing us of any changes to your e-mail address and other contact details.
Changes To Our Privacy Policy
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our Site.
Your rights
You have the right to ask for a copy of the Data held by us in our records in return for which we may charge a small fee. You also have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your Data.
Privacy policy
Buy from Mackaysonline shop
Find your nearest Mackays stockist
Enter postcode
Follow us
@mackays_jams
/mackays.jams
/mackaysjams
